<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 04:01:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-21 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsycckbcc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsycckbcc/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-06 17:30 OpenShift - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Agenda: - Kubernetes versus a full cloud platform such as OpenShift. - Briefly the PSD2 solution. - The microservice architecture of the PSD2 service and how it leverages the capabilities of Kubernetes Seminarie leader: Eero Arvonen who work as a solution ar...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-09-28 17:30 Lärdomar från entreprenören bakom produktbolaget Black Cat - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vill du lära dig mer om hur det är att driva ett produktbolag från start?Vill du höra om misstagen från en annan entreprenör, kanske för att inte göra samma misstag själv? Agenda:Bolagsform för/nackdel Stegvis Design/tillverkning/import/Sälj/marknadsföring/Likvidite...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-29 18:00 Code 'n' Chill Meetup - Norrköping Software Development]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had the idea that we could code some stuff outside together. So basically bring your laptops and projects. If you don't have a project or laptop and just would like to chat and/or learn a bit from others, that's a great opportunity to do so.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Norrkoping-Software-Development/events/278851764/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Norrkoping-Software-Development/events/278851764/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-08-26 17:30 The power of UX Design and what you should know - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Topic: - The Power of User Experience Design and what you should know Agenda: - A bit of history for context - Gain clarity about the buzzwords & titels you might have heard - How it works, what are the process and tools that can be used - Return...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-23 19:00 Discussing ASTROLOGY of 2021-2025  (Advance level) Meetup  - Stockholm Spiritual & Crypto "DigiNomads" meetup group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Very interesting times ahead! Since astrologers see the world from very wide perspective normally feel misunderstood speaking to people. however when astrologer meets astrologer it immediately feels home. January 2020 (Saturn & Pluto conjunct in Capricron) th...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-spiritual-crypto-diginomads-meetup-group/events/279551848/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-spiritual-crypto-diginomads-meetup-group/events/279551848/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-21 18:00 Afterwork Hacking @ Comfort Hotel Westeras - Västerås Coffee and Code]]></title><description><![CDATA[Beroende på Corona-situationen så blir det inga möten på onsdagar en tid framöver.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Vasteras-Coffee-and-Code/events/rhdvbsycckbcc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Vasteras-Coffee-and-Code/events/rhdvbsycckbcc/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-21 19:00 Digital nomad (in Stockholm) Planning travels for Fall 2021 - Stockholm Spiritual & Crypto "DigiNomads" meetup group]]></title><description><![CDATA[These days to most people traveling is brave thing to do. (PCR, certifications and changing restrictions, blablabla ..). But for "Real digital nomads" (also of "location independent" guys) No excuses!! Travel restrictions in most cases works to our favor; low cost oppor...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-spiritual-crypto-diginomads-meetup-group/events/279551563/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-spiritual-crypto-diginomads-meetup-group/events/279551563/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-09-29 19:00 Embedded systems in the real world and how you can get started - Örnsköldsvik Developer Meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[The last Wednesday of every month we invite you to a meetup at HouseBe Örnsköldsvik. This time we'll learn from how BAE Systems build high performance embedded systems. We'll also take a step back and look at how you can get started with building at home. This ovik.dev ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/ovik-dev/events/276707734/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/ovik-dev/events/276707734/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-08-25 19:00 Using Blockchain technology for a more sustainable and transparent world - Örnsköldsvik Developer Meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[The last Wednesday of every month we invite you to a meetup at HouseBe Örnsköldsvik. This time we'll learn from Mats Hälldahl, who is the National Blockchain Lead Sweden at Atea, how we can use blockchain technology to build the transparent and resilient solutions of the futur...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/ovik-dev/events/276707730/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/ovik-dev/events/276707730/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-07-20 17:00 #tredjetisdagen]]></title><description><![CDATA[Om det som är viktigt. Det brukar kretsa kring internet på något sätt, men det beror ju mest på att internet är överallt. // About what's important. Usually it will evolve around the internet in some way, but that's because internet is everywhere.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/tredjetisdagen/events/dgtxpfycckbbc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/tredjetisdagen/events/dgtxpfycckbbc/</guid></item></channel></rss>