<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 17:02:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-10 08:00 Nordic IT Security - Live TV Brooadcast - Nordic It Security Forum - Sthlm chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[A groundbreaking Live TV studio and digital show with an awe-inspiring speaker line-up, in-depth interviews, and interactive round table discussions. You can check the whole Agenda here: https://nor...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-04 17:00 VNTRS - HealthTech startups & the tech behind it! - VNTRS Knowledge Night]]></title><description><![CDATA[FYI: This event will be at the VNTRS office in Fridhemsplan and therefore has a limit of 30 people who will be able to attend the event. It's time for our third VNTRS Knowledge Night💥 This time we will hear the story of two of our portfolio companies within Heal...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/VNTRS-Knowledge-Night/events/273875261/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/VNTRS-Knowledge-Night/events/273875261/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-18 17:30 Agil HR - Agil Målstyrning och OKR - Agil HR - Agile HR]]></title><description><![CDATA[Välkommen till nästa Agil HR-meetup där vi har bjudit in Sara Hjärtberg, Head of People & Culture på MAG Interactive för att diskutera Agil målstyrning – beteendeförändring för ökad motivation och bättre kundnytta. Vi kommer utgå från Agil HR och dela med oss av pra...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-05 17:00 Open Source Integration - It Is All About Integration - Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Niclas Tenggren and Arul Madoneraj will give som insights in open source integration, Do not miss this ocation. There is an additional slot available for anyone that would like to share.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/273476584/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/273476584/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-26 17:00 WebAuth, Framtiden för autentisering på webben - Backend Developers Stockholm Meetup Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Backend Developers Stockholm välkomnar er till årets första meetup som arrangeras tillsammans med Yubico och Utvecklarbolaget. Ämnet är "WebAuthn" som kommer att presenteras av Emil Lundberg på Yubico. Det är begränsat antal platser så först till kvarn.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-12 18:00 STOCKHOLM TECH JOB FAIR 2020 - Stockholm TechMeetups]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome Employers and Job Seekers! Whether you are looking for a job or recruiting, Tech Job Fair is the place to be! The speed dating event for recruiting! Come to meet employers, ask questions, and make connections. This event will target local job seekers from...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-17 17:30 Let's Talk About Smart Buildings @ QueensLab - Let's talk about UX]]></title><description><![CDATA[In November, we're visiting our friends at QueensLab in their new space Walborg Ventures. The theme for this evening will be "smart buildings" and we have prepared a fun design challenge for you guys to take on if you want...! See you there!]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/lets-talk-about-ux/events/274074497/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/lets-talk-about-ux/events/274074497/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-10-29 17:30 Startup Dojo S09E03 - Malmö Startups]]></title><description><![CDATA[STARTUP DOJO is Virtual and Onsite! See https://www.foocafe.org/event/startup-dojo-entrepreneurs-entrepreneurs-4 for details. It is time for your favourite monthly ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Malmo-Startups/events/tvtmsrybcnbdc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Malmo-Startups/events/tvtmsrybcnbdc/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-10-28 17:30 Flutter news, experiments and examples of Flutter on the job - Lund Flutter Meetup Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let’s do it again! Meet up, have some food+beverages and share some Flutter stories. This time the event will be held in Helsingborg at MindPark 28/10 17:30-20:30. The arrangement will be Corona adjusted with lots of space at the event facilities and with a limit...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Lund-Flutter-Meetup-Group/events/273291047/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Lund-Flutter-Meetup-Group/events/273291047/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-26 17:30 Startup Dojo S09E04 - Malmö Startups]]></title><description><![CDATA[STARTUP DOJO is Virtual and Onsite! See https://www.foocafe.org/event/startup-dojo-entrepreneurs-entrepreneurs-4 for details. It is time for your favourite monthly startup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Malmo-Startups/events/tvtmsrybcpbjc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Malmo-Startups/events/tvtmsrybcpbjc/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-10-24 10:00 Malmö Event (In-Person) : Build a food delivery app - Flutter and Firebase - Google Developers Group - GDG West Sweden]]></title><description><![CDATA[Everything you need to know to get your app online fast. In partners with GDG Copenhagen, we Meet in Malmo, In this workshop, We will build an App using flutter and Firebase. The choices you need to make what products you can use to build an app . We will go zero to...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/GDGWestSweden/events/273550474/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/GDGWestSweden/events/273550474/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-05 16:00 Customer data: A force for good or evil? - Digital/Data Analyst Lovers of Skåne]]></title><description><![CDATA[Data collection happens everywhere. The amount of digital data that exists is growing at a rapid rate, doubling every two years, and changing the way we live. By the year 2020, about 1.7 megabytes of new information will be created every second for every human being on the pla...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/meetup-group-igkpmarp/events/274053281/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/meetup-group-igkpmarp/events/274053281/</guid></item></channel></rss>