<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Göteborg)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:01:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/goteborg.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-16 17:00 OWASP GBG & CloudNativeGBG  "The sequel" - OWASP Gothenburg Chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yes you've read that correctly, once again CloudNativeGBG joins us for some cool talks. This time we turn things around. Instead of how one could hack the Cloud, that the talks was about at the last event. We now take on how do we Secure the Cloud? ---> As this i...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282364562/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282364562/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-09 17:30 OWASP GBG Secure Coding Tournament - OWASP Gothenburg Chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just when the cold winter is upon us, we at OWASP GBG heat things up with a security tournament! Try your skills in a set of tasks designed to help developers build secure coding skills. The tournament is aimed at developers interested in security with challenges of var...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282364274/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282364274/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-16 17:30 Winter Tech Quiz with Devies - Devies Gothenburg]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi Guys, We will on the 16th of December have a tech-quiz at our office and you are welcome! The quiz will start at 17:30 and it will be held by a tech-savvy quizmaster. To be a part of our quiz you need to sign up with a team of 2-5 people. Sign up to...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Devies-Gothenburg/events/282188726/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Devies-Gothenburg/events/282188726/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 17:30 Here we Go again! @ InterEast - Go West]]></title><description><![CDATA[It has been a while! But we hope you are all still around, coding Go like never before and are hungry to come join us again for the first post-Covid Go West meetup hosted by InterEast! During this time, the Go team has been busy cooking up perhaps the biggest change to ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/sweden-go-west/events/282165054/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/sweden-go-west/events/282165054/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-02 07:30 Frukostföreläsning på Infotiv - Science! by Infotiv]]></title><description><![CDATA[Då höstens Science! by Infotiv genomförs både fysiskt på plats och digitalt, har vi denna separata anmälan till eventet på plats. Frukost serveras från kl 07:30 och föredraget startar kl 08:00. Anmäl dig till online-eventet för att få uppdaterad information om fö...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Science-by-Infotiv/events/281709112/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Science-by-Infotiv/events/281709112/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 17:30 Research through design - Got UX - An IxDA local chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Did you miss us? It's finally time to meet again and nerd out together in person! 🎉 To kick things off, we have Mehmet Aydın Baytaş, researcher at Chalmers Department of Computer Science and creator of Design Disciplin, to talk to us about "Research through Design."]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/got-ux/events/282188738/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/got-ux/events/282188738/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-09 16:00 Äntligen Delphi-möte igen! - Användargruppen för Delphi i Göteborg]]></title><description><![CDATA[Efter lång väntan vill Alfasoft äntligen bjuda in dig på ett nytt Delphi Meetup. Ett event för nya och gamla Delphi (och C++Builder) utvecklare oavsett erfarenhet och kompetens. På vår Meetup-sammankomst kommer vi att prata högt och lågt om Delphi och få en unik möjlighet att ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/delphi-gbg/events/281969014/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/delphi-gbg/events/281969014/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-07 18:00 Rust Gbg — December 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[[Do you want to do a talk this month or in the future? Please let me know!] Please note The Techno Creatives has moved address in the last 400 years! Check the map for details. Kick off will be around 18:00, with some pizza (vegan and vegetarian options - please ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/rustgbg/events/282184713/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/rustgbg/events/282184713/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-07 18:00 Scrum Beers - Workshop: Solving long-lasting issues - Scrum Beers Göteborg]]></title><description><![CDATA[WHAT? Learn how to approach and solve long-lasting issues in you company! HOW? A workshop to try out the Liberating Structure "Discovery & Action Dialogue". ht...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Scrum-beers-Goteborg/events/282270191/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Scrum-beers-Goteborg/events/282270191/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-02 17:30 OWASP SäkPub - OWASP Gothenburg Chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[Winter is coming, dark times are upon us. The next Meltdown is lurking like a Spectre in the shadows. In other words: A perfect time to meet up and discuss our defences! There is no specific theme for this pub-meet but as always there is security on the agenda! S...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282254317/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/owasp-gothenburg-meetup-group/events/282254317/</guid></item></channel></rss>