<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Malmö)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 22:01:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/malmo.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 17:30 Intro to Neo4j: The Data Science Graph Database - Neo4j-Öresund]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hosted by our friends at Data Science Malmö and taking place at Foo Café, we're pleased to introduce you to using Neo4j for graph data science. Join Data Science Malmö over at https://www.meetup.com/...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Neo4j-Oresund/events/281418056/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Neo4j-Oresund/events/281418056/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-06 17:30 A Simple Explanation of SPF, DKIM and DMARC and its Role for Email - DevOps Malmö]]></title><description><![CDATA[Register here: https://foocafe.org/event/simple-explanation-spf-dkim-and-dmarc-and-its-role-email Abstract: Where mail and DNS TXT meet. Understanding ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/DevOpsMalmo/events/282264898/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/DevOpsMalmo/events/282264898/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-30 08:30 Startup Coffee Meetup ☕️  - Skåne Startups]]></title><description><![CDATA[80% of your future business success will come just from 20% of your existing relationships.  Everyone is welcome on our Startup Coffee Meetup ☕️ Every other Tuesday with SkåneStartups and Goto10. You don’t have to prepare in any way. This is a safe space where entrepreneu...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/skane-startups/events/282184140/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/skane-startups/events/282184140/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-02 17:15 Microsoft Ignite Azure Skåne]]></title><description><![CDATA[Azure Skåne is happy to invite you to this Microsoft Ignite Watch Party hosted by Johan Åhlén (Azure MVP) and Michael Jonsson (Azure MVP). This will be a hybrid event, taking place at Foo Café in Malmö as well as online through YouTube. We will watch a video and ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Azure-Skane/events/281497368/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Azure-Skane/events/281497368/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-30 17:30 Tales of ethical hacking: war stories from ten years of penetration testing - Joint Academy Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[Joint Academy is hosting a meetup at the Malmö office Nov 30th. Linus Kvarnhammar from the SVT show ”Hackad” will give some behind-the-scenes anecdotes from the TV-show. Linus will also talk about cases he has worked with during his 10 years of ethical hacking. On top of that ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/joint-academy-tech/events/281815343/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/joint-academy-tech/events/281815343/</guid></item></channel></rss>