<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 12:01:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-11 17:30 Teaser: Kubernetes - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kubernetes is an open-source container-orchestration system for automating application deployment, scaling, and management. It was originally designed by Google, and is now maintained by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation. Mikael is a consultant at West Forest Techno...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/264053926/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/264053926/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-18 17:30 Lärdomar från entreprenören bakom produktbolaget Black Cat - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vill du lära dig mer om hur det är att driva ett produktbolag från start?Vill du höra om misstagen från en annan entreprenör, kanske för att inte göra samma misstag själv? Agenda:Bolagsform för/nackdel Stegvis Design/tillverkning/import/Sälj/marknadsföring/Likvidite...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-27 15:30 Stockholm OPA meetup with Styra and Avassa - Stockholm OPA users]]></title><description><![CDATA[Curious or experienced with Open Policy Agent. Anders Eknert dev Advocate at OPA will talk about the latest news and updates on OPA Anders and Fredrik from Avassa will give an example on how to use OPA in an edge computing use case. Your are welcome from 15.00 and ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-opa-meetup/events/281066231/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/stockholm-opa-meetup/events/281066231/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-26 19:00 Hackathon 2021 - Sweden University Challenge - BeMyApp events - EMEA]]></title><description><![CDATA[Huawei Sweden hackathon is back! Are you ready to challenge your creativity, assess your problem-solving skills, and demonstrate your team working capabilities for the shot at a SEK 100,000 prize pool? 👇 The challenge: Huawei is inviting innovative computer science...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/BeMyApp-events/events/281355399/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/BeMyApp-events/events/281355399/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-25 19:00 Swedish Power BI User Group Meetup - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA['This is an external event, created by The Swedish Power BI User Group that will be hosted at the Microsoft Reactor Stockholm´s premises. For registration, please go to their Meetup page.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/281374614/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/281374614/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-21 17:30 DIY data diode - 0xFF]]></title><description><![CDATA[Data diodes are expensive network devices used in high security environments where a normal firewall just isn’t trustworthy enough. Why are they so expensive and how difficult is it to build one yourself? In this talk Magnus will show you how to build your own gigabit d...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/0xFFse/events/281480105/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/0xFFse/events/281480105/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-21 18:00 En miljon dagliga kunder, fyra storefronts, ett komponentbibliotek - DevForum-Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Många av oss älskar idéen av ett väldesignat och välbyggt komponentbibliotek. Ett ställe där du hittar precis den komponenten du behöver som ser ut och funkar precis som den ska. Men är det verkligen så lätt? Tydligen inte. På Ellos Group, byggde vi eg-ui. Ett delat kom...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/DevForum/events/281087931/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/DevForum/events/281087931/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-25 12:00 Health and Innovation days #1 Biohacking - BioNyfiken - Biohackers in Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[**Important note: RSVP link is down below** In the first of a series of events organized at Epicenter, in Stockholm, you can learn more about: "how and why you should aim for living to 120" What can we all do to improve our chances for a longer and healthier life? A...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/BioNyfiken-Sthlm/events/281403476/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/BioNyfiken-Sthlm/events/281403476/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-27 17:00 NFTs and MEGA GOSSIP catch-up IRL+AW - Decentralized Camp - Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[FINNNNAALLLYYYYYYY! After a long and painful era of covid-19, it is NOW time to start doing physical Decentralized Camp meetups. We miss you all and we all have so much to talk about - blockchain, NFT, L0, L1, L2, interledger, TPS, wallets, sidechains, zksnarks, Metaverse,...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/decentralized-camp/events/281373527/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/decentralized-camp/events/281373527/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-19 17:30 Jfokus Foo Bar - Jforum Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[We miss to see you all in person! We felt that we needed a place just to hang-out after office hours. We found Kungsbiljarden! The bar offers a solid range of drinks with something for everyone. Beer in the form of IPA, pale ale, ale, lager, pilsner, witbier, weissbier ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Jforum-Stockholm/events/281201517/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Jforum-Stockholm/events/281201517/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-19 17:30 The power of UX Design and what you should know - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Topic: - The Power of User Experience Design and what you should know Agenda: - A bit of history for context - Gain clarity about the buzzwords & titels you might have heard - How it works, what are the process and tools that can be used - Return...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-08 18:00 STHLM TECH Meetup w/ Unicorn Angels]]></title><description><![CDATA[Join the event on this page, but you MUST register at www.sthlmtech.com STHLM TECH Meetup is Europe's largest gathering of startups each month. Kry, Truecaller, Spotify are not only Sweden's hottest unicorns, they are also the source of Sweden's newest and most a...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/STHLM-Tech-Meetup/events/281485084/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/STHLM-Tech-Meetup/events/281485084/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 07:00 E-Commerce Tech Global Summit'21 - Geekle]]></title><description><![CDATA[E-Commerce is continuously growing and can grow even more. Although online shopping has become one of the foremost popular online activities, the planet of eCommerce has become more competitive. To stay competitive, organizations have to monitor new 2021 eCommerce trends const...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/https-geekle-us/events/281351970/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/https-geekle-us/events/281351970/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-11 14:00 OpenInfra Forum #10!  - OpenInfra User Group Sweden]]></title><description><![CDATA[Update: Hello everyone, sadly the 25 burgers are gone. But for the rest of you, you are most welcome to the event, and there will be vendors there who might be willing to pay for your burger + beer if you are nice to them! =) 28 seats remaining until the venue is full, ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/OpenStack-User-Group-Sweden/events/281206331/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/OpenStack-User-Group-Sweden/events/281206331/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-21 17:00 Owasp Stockholm DevOps and security & Benefits of Cloud Thinking - OWASP Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to a OWASP Stockholm event! Finally we can meet IRL again and we will fire off with a Secure Development event hosted by Omegapoint at their new office site. Location: Jakobsbergsgatan 24, Auditorium. Time: October 21, 17.00 – 20.00 Lighter food &...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/owasp-stockholm/events/281022013/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/owasp-stockholm/events/281022013/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-20 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccnbbc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccnbbc/</guid></item></channel></rss>