<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:01:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-11 17:30 Teaser: Kubernetes - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kubernetes is an open-source container-orchestration system for automating application deployment, scaling, and management. It was originally designed by Google, and is now maintained by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation. Mikael is a consultant at West Forest Techno...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/264053926/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/264053926/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-18 17:30 Lärdomar från entreprenören bakom produktbolaget Black Cat - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vill du lära dig mer om hur det är att driva ett produktbolag från start?Vill du höra om misstagen från en annan entreprenör, kanske för att inte göra samma misstag själv? Agenda:Bolagsform för/nackdel Stegvis Design/tillverkning/import/Sälj/marknadsföring/Likvidite...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268655135/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-04 10:00 WTD Prague / Watch party @Peltarion / Day 1 - Write the Docs Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Watch party - Day 1 We can't go to Prague so let's have a watch party together in Stockholm. I've booked two conference rooms @Peltarion—one where we can watch the main talk and one where you can join the unconference. We want to keep the spirit of Write the Doc...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Write-the-Docs-Stockholm/events/280764559/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Write-the-Docs-Stockholm/events/280764559/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-09-29 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccmbmc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccmbmc/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-15 09:00 Säkerhetskollen - Dataföreningen Meet&Learn Stockholmskretsen]]></title><description><![CDATA[Är du orolig över säkerheten i din mobil? Att hackare kan ta över den och stjäla information eller pengar? Eller att appar spionerar på vad du gör och var du är? Välkommen den 15 oktober till Dataföreningen på Fleminggatan 7 i Stockholm. Studerande från Xenter Yrkeshögs...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Dataforeningen-Meet-Learn/events/280485588/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Dataforeningen-Meet-Learn/events/280485588/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-19 17:30 The power of UX Design and what you should know - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Topic: - The Power of User Experience Design and what you should know Agenda: - A bit of history for context - Gain clarity about the buzzwords & titels you might have heard - How it works, what are the process and tools that can be used - Return...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-10-05 10:00 WTD Prague / Watch party @Peltarion / Day 2 - Write the Docs Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Watch party - Day 2. We can't go to Prague so let's have a watch party together in Stockholm. I've booked two conference rooms @Peltarion—one where we can watch the main talk and one where you can join the unconference. We want to keep the spirit of Write the Do...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Write-the-Docs-Stockholm/events/280766036/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Write-the-Docs-Stockholm/events/280766036/</guid></item></channel></rss>