<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 15:01:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 18:00 SvelteSummit Mini Edition: Stockholm - Svelte Society Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[YouTube link for online viewers: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=khYZmMiSHm8 Svelte Society Sweden Discord: https://discord.gg/R2WWaYHG8W]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/svelte-society-stockholm/events/282020687/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/svelte-society-stockholm/events/282020687/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-09 08:30 A how-to guide to Switching Careers into IT  - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this event about? This session has been designed to help support people who are cons...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282049987/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282049987/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2022-02-08 17:30 OpenShift - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Agenda: - Kubernetes versus a full cloud platform such as OpenShift. - Briefly the PSD2 solution. - The microservice architecture of the PSD2 service and how it leverages the capabilities of Kubernetes Seminarie leader: Eero Arvonen who work as a solution ar...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-03 13:00 Hack your CV - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this event about? Have you recently moved to Sweden and are looking for your first j...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041174/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041174/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-07 17:30 Gender Inequality in Tech - Why Is it a problem and How can we fix it? - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this event about? The tech space is full of opportunities, but as a woman in a male ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041966/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041966/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 12:00 The Secrets of a Successful IT Career - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this session about? In this session Alan will share his experiences on what he sees ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282042084/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282042084/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-02 17:00 Omvärldsanalys - Vart är prestandatest på väg? - Prestandaforum Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hej allesammans! Äntligen är restriktionerna släppta och vi kan återigen börja "meetup:a" på riktigt med vännerna i Prestandaforum Sthlm :) Behovet men framförallt hur men arbetar med prestandatester är under ständig förändring och flera aktörer går mer mot shift...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Prestandaforum-Stockholm/events/281709537/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Prestandaforum-Stockholm/events/281709537/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-09 17:30 Så skapade ICA ett ekosystem för sina tjänster med GCP - Stockholm Cloud Analytics]]></title><description><![CDATA[Det ICA har genomfört är enormt spännande och därför välkomnar vi dig att träffa Olof Granberg, Director of Data and Advanced Analytics Technology på ICA, när han berättar om deras Google Cloud Platform-resa och hur dataplattformen sattes upp. Highlights ur programmet: ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Cloud-Analytics/events/282263039/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Cloud-Analytics/events/282263039/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-03 12:00 Swedish for IT professionals - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this event about? This session is hosted by SFX and SFX-IT, which is an extended cou...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041212/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041212/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-07 18:00 TFUG Stockholm First Meetup  - TensorFlow User Group Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the first meetup for the TensorFlow User Group Stockholm! We will have this event in-person at the Stockholm Google office. If you can't make it in person don't worry, we will also send out a link so you can join online. Here is the agenda for our firs...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/tensorflow-user-group-stockholm/events/282244624/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/tensorflow-user-group-stockholm/events/282244624/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 17:00 Jfokus Foo Bar Christmas edition - Jforum Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jfokus Foo Bar is having a Christmas edition! Come, get a beer and mingle! The bar offers a solid range of drinks with something for everyone. Beer in the form of IPA, pale ale, ale, lager, pilsner, witbier, weissbier and stout as well as a wine list with most varieties...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Jforum-Stockholm/events/281949957/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Jforum-Stockholm/events/281949957/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 08:30 Five Surprising skills To Land Your Next Job in IT  - Microsoft Reactor Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[* This is an in-person event, and pre-registartion is required. Seats are limited so if you can no longer attend, please cancel your ticket to make room for someone else. What is this event about? You may think you’re not cut out for IT because you don’t have the...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041516/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Microsoft-Reactor-Stockholm/events/282041516/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 07:00 E-Commerce Tech Global Summit'21 - Geekle]]></title><description><![CDATA[E-Commerce is continuously growing and can grow even more. Although online shopping has become one of the foremost popular online activities, the planet of eCommerce has become more competitive. To stay competitive, organizations have to monitor new 2021 eCommerce trends const...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/https-geekle-us/events/281351970/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/https-geekle-us/events/281351970/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-12-01 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccqbcb/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/gfnqbsyccqbcb/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021-11-29 18:00 STHLM TECH Meetup w/ J12, Northzone, Industrifonden]]></title><description><![CDATA[Join the event on this page, but you MUST register at https://sthlm-tech-meetup-with-j12-northzone.confetti.events/ STHLM TECH Meetup is Europe's largest gathering of startups ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/STHLM-Tech-Meetup/events/282141487/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/STHLM-Tech-Meetup/events/282141487/</guid></item></channel></rss>