<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 18:02:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-10 08:00 Nordic IT Security - Live TV Brooadcast - Nordic It Security Forum - Sthlm chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[A groundbreaking Live TV studio and digital show with an awe-inspiring speaker line-up, in-depth interviews, and interactive round table discussions. You can check the whole Agenda here: https://nor...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-04 17:00 VNTRS - HealthTech startups & the tech behind it! - VNTRS Knowledge Night]]></title><description><![CDATA[FYI: This event will be at the VNTRS office in Fridhemsplan and therefore has a limit of 30 people who will be able to attend the event. It's time for our third VNTRS Knowledge Night💥 This time we will hear the story of two of our portfolio companies within Heal...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/VNTRS-Knowledge-Night/events/273875261/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/VNTRS-Knowledge-Night/events/273875261/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-18 17:30 Agil HR - Agil Målstyrning och OKR - Agil HR - Agile HR]]></title><description><![CDATA[Välkommen till nästa Agil HR-meetup där vi har bjudit in Sara Hjärtberg, Head of People & Culture på MAG Interactive för att diskutera Agil målstyrning – beteendeförändring för ökad motivation och bättre kundnytta. Vi kommer utgå från Agil HR och dela med oss av pra...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-05 17:00 Open Source Integration - It Is All About Integration - Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Niclas Tenggren and Arul Madoneraj will give som insights in open source integration, to make it even more hands-on Madhan Rajendran will do a live demo of the topics discussed in theory. Hoping the demo Gods are with us. Do not miss this ocation! There is an additiona...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/273476584/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/273476584/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-26 17:00 WebAuth, Framtiden för autentisering på webben - Backend Developers Stockholm Meetup Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Backend Developers Stockholm välkomnar er till årets första meetup som arrangeras tillsammans med Yubico och Utvecklarbolaget. Ämnet är "WebAuthn" som kommer att presenteras av Emil Lundberg på Yubico. Det är begränsat antal platser så först till kvarn.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-12 18:00 STOCKHOLM TECH JOB FAIR 2020 - Stockholm TechMeetups]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome Employers and Job Seekers! Whether you are looking for a job or recruiting, Tech Job Fair is the place to be! The speed dating event for recruiting! Come to meet employers, ask questions, and make connections. This event will target local job seekers from...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</guid></item></channel></rss>