<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 01:02:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-10 08:00 Nordic IT Security - Live TV Brooadcast - Nordic It Security Forum - Sthlm chapter]]></title><description><![CDATA[A groundbreaking Live TV studio and digital show with an awe-inspiring speaker line-up, in-depth interviews, and interactive round table discussions. You can check the whole Agenda here: https://nor...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-It-Security-Forum-Sthlm-chapter/events/273950561/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-04 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/qvtrhkybcpbgb/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/qvtrhkybcpbgb/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-18 17:30 Agil HR - Agil Målstyrning och OKR - Agil HR - Agile HR]]></title><description><![CDATA[Välkommen till nästa Agil HR-meetup där vi har bjudit in Sara Hjärtberg, Head of People & Culture på MAG Interactive för att diskutera Agil målstyrning – beteendeförändring för ökad motivation och bättre kundnytta. Vi kommer utgå från Agil HR och dela med oss av pra...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Agil-HR-Agile-HR/events/273820657/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-26 17:00 WebAuth, Framtiden för autentisering på webben - Backend Developers Stockholm Meetup Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Backend Developers Stockholm välkomnar er till årets första meetup som arrangeras tillsammans med Yubico och Utvecklarbolaget. Ämnet är "WebAuthn" som kommer att presenteras av Emil Lundberg på Yubico. Det är begränsat antal platser så först till kvarn.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-12 18:00 STOCKHOLM TECH JOB FAIR 2020 - Stockholm TechMeetups]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome Employers and Job Seekers! Whether you are looking for a job or recruiting, Tech Job Fair is the place to be! The speed dating event for recruiting! Come to meet employers, ask questions, and make connections. This event will target local job seekers from...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</guid></item></channel></rss>