<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Swedish Tech Events (Stockholm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Events for developers, technologists, and other geeks in Sweden]]></description><link>https://swedishtechevents.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:01:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swedishtechevents.com/feeds/stockholm.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2020-09-15 17:30 How to scale your landing zones in Azure - Foo Café Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[This evening Anders Jansson (CSA, Microsoft) will share the latest news, how you can build with control, with code and follow Azure design guidelines. The enterprise-scale architecture is modular by design. It allows you to start with foundational landing zones that sup...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/foocafe/events/272977346/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/foocafe/events/272977346/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-09-09 08:00 This weeks Lean Coffee - Stockholm Lean Coffee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like to limit WIP (Work-In-Process), visualization of workflows and self-organizing teams? Want to meet others like you and learn more about Lean and Agile? We are few enthusiasts who meet every Wednesday morning since May 2010, to exchange thoughts and experiences over a cup ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/qvtrhkybcmbmb/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-Lean-Coffee/events/qvtrhkybcmbmb/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-10-06 17:30 OpenShift - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Agenda: - Kubernetes versus a full cloud platform such as OpenShift. - Briefly the PSD2 solution. - The microservice architecture of the PSD2 service and how it leverages the capabilities of Kubernetes Seminarie leader: Eero Arvonen who work as a solution ar...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268625807/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-07 08:00 Nordic Summit - Stockholm - Nordic Summit - Denmark]]></title><description><![CDATA[You're familiar with your local CRM user groups. This event will bring together CRM user groups from all Nordic countries in order to share knowledge across borders. We will have 5 tracks for a total of 30 sessions. The venue will be filled with great talent and lots of...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-Summit-Denmark/events/269324567/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Nordic-Summit-Denmark/events/269324567/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-09-16 17:00 WebAuth, Framtiden för autentisering på webben - Backend Developers Stockholm Meetup Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[Backend Developers Stockholm välkomnar er till årets första meetup som arrangeras tillsammans med Yubico och Utvecklarbolaget. Ämnet är "WebAuthn" som kommer att presenteras av Emil Lundberg på Yubico. Det är begränsat antal platser så först till kvarn.]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Backend-Developers-Stockholm-Meetup-Group/events/269320633/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-11-12 18:00 STOCKHOLM TECH JOB FAIR 2020 - Stockholm TechMeetups]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome Employers and Job Seekers! Whether you are looking for a job or recruiting, Tech Job Fair is the place to be! The speed dating event for recruiting! Come to meet employers, ask questions, and make connections. This event will target local job seekers from...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Stockholm-TechMeetups/events/266824796/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-10-20 17:30 The power of UX Design and what you should know - West Forest Tech meetup]]></title><description><![CDATA[Topic: - The Power of User Experience Design and what you should know Agenda: - A bit of history for context - Gain clarity about the buzzwords & titels you might have heard - How it works, what are the process and tools that can be used - Return...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/West-Forest-Tech-meetup-HW-SW-MEK/events/268583103/</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[2020-09-10 17:00 Seamless customer journey  - It Is All About Integration - Stockholm]]></title><description><![CDATA[Seamless customer journey. With APIs or other... One presenter ready. Want to add please be welcome... If Corona stops us will be changed to on line. Crossing our fingers. With keeping our distance and taking care of ourself we will meet in a small first meetup in ...]]></description><link>https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/271420283/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/It-is-all-about-Integration/events/271420283/</guid></item></channel></rss>